<odoo>
    <data noupdate="1">
        <record id="timesheet_tip_1" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">Timesheets are the lifeblood of our company; they have a direct impact on revenues.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_3" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">It's part of the job to search for information. These hours should also be billable.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_4" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">Make it a habit to record timesheets every day.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_6" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">If you’re unsure if something is billable, just log it. You deserve credit.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_7" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">Any time spent interacting with others—whether it’s a quick call, a meeting, or an informal chat—is valuable and should be recorded.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_8" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">Time spent troubleshooting or resolving unexpected issues is still work. Don’t forget to include it in your timesheet.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_9" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">Consistently tracking your time ensures no effort, big or small, goes unnoticed.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_10" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">Don’t second-guess whether something “counts”—if you’ve spent time on it, it belongs in your timesheet.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_11" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">Organizing, planning, or reviewing your work is part of the job and should be logged like any other task.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_12" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">Preparation is crucial for successful meetings. Always include the time you spend getting ready in your timesheet.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_13" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">Small administrative tasks keep operations running smoothly. Don’t forget to include them in your timesheet.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_14" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">When you share your knowledge with clients or teammates, that time is valuable. Be sure to track it accurately.</field>
        </record>
        <record id="timesheet_tip_15" model="hr.timesheet.tip">
            <field name="name">By maintaining clear timesheets, you demonstrate your dedication and help build trust—your effort truly matters!</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>
